

# SIMRAN WADHAWAN

## PERSONAL SUMMARY

I am an energetic, enthusiastic and self-motivated student in my fourth and last year at university, that brings forth a motivated attitude and a variety of powerful skills due to my experience. I am passionate about growth and have always indulged in gaining experiences through extra-curricular activities alongside my studies.

# Auckland

**\** 0278618391

in Linkedin.com/in/simranwadhawan

## **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR OF COMMERCE**

THE UNIVERSITY OF AUCKLAND

#### Majoring in Marketing

Related coursework: Contemporary marketing, Marketing research, Consumer Behaviour, Sustainable Marketing, Advertising and Branding

## Majoring in Information Systems

Related coursework: Business systems analysis, Digital Systems, Database Systems, Global IT strategy, Enterprise Systems.

#### **BACHELOR OF SCIENCE**

THE UNIVERSITY OF AUCKLAND

## Majoring in Psychology

Related coursework: Mind & Behaviour, Attitude formation & Personality, Lifespan development, Research Methods, Cultural development

## Majoring in Statistics

Related coursework: Introduction to Stats, Applied Time Series Analysis, Applied Multivariate Analysis, Digital Technologies,

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

#### SHOPPER MARKETING INTERN

## THE GRIFFIN'S FOOD COMPANY | NOV 2021 - FEB 2022

- First-hand experience in the FMCG industry via the FMCG Future Me Internship Programme 2021
- Supported Shopper marketing Manager with rollout of campaigns and activation plans of new product developments and limited time offer products into stores, under various supermarket banners – Countdown, New World, Pak 'n' Save etc.
- Reviewed and approved artwork for campaigns
- Co-led multiple projects launches simultaneously (four, in the duration of the internship), alongside the design, distribution and activation agencies
- Managed distribution of samples to customers and agencies
- Managed regular communication of activation plans to field sales team and brand team
- Administrative support and managing approvals, including the legal team
- Activation plan and implementation leadership of biscuit launch
- Updated sales, marketing and field teams on campaign design and implementation

#### **SOLE DIRECTOR, OWNER & EMPLOYEE**

## BINARY EVENT STYLING LIMITED | MARCH 2020 - PRESENT

- Founded an event styling and management company, requiring me to adapt to different roles styling, graphic design, branding, marketing, public relations, logistics, accounting, admin and etc.
- The company is now highly recognized within the industry, and brokeeven within five months of business
- The average amount of events/clients per month is increasing heavily
- Currently working at full capacity and handling multiple events and projects simultaneously (4-5 events a week)

### **CO-PRESIDENT**

## AUCKLAND UNIVERSITY COMMERECE STUDENTS' ASSOCIATION | NOV 2021- PRESENT

- AUCSA is one of the biggest faculty associations at The University of Auckland, representing the Business School and its students.
- Part of the Student Council Board, Student Consultative Group and a chair of the Faculty-level Staff Student Consultative Committee, alongside the associate Dean of the Business School.

## **SKILLS**

- Fast Paced and quick, with great attention to detail
- Independent and reliable, yet a team player
- Collaboration and Motivation Skills
- Project Management Skills
- Strategic Planning Abilities
- Strong Communication Skills
- Content Creation and social media management
- Confident with Public Speaking and Presenting (extroverted)
- Leadership and management Skills
- Coding (SQL, R Studio, HTML)
- Graphic Design (Adobe InDesign, Photoshop, illustrator and Canva)
- EPC Modelling (Aris)
- ERP Database modelling
- Microsoft Office (Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Project, Outlook)

# REFERENCES

# **Moon Ban**

Shopper Marketing Manager The Griffin's Food Company Moon.ban@griffins.co.nz 0275704638

#### Yashri Patel

Vice-President Auckland University Commerce Students' Association vp@aucsa.org 0226924181

- Manage a team of 10 executive members, responsible for various components of the association
- Planning and organisation of social and professional development events

   creating a cohesive university culture for students, whilst providing
  multiple professional opportunities for students to learn from.
- Onboarding and managing external relations such as Sponsors and Partnerships. Under my co-presidency we have PwC, EY, CA ANZ, CPA and Robot Hub as Gold sponsors. Deloitte, FMCG Future Me Programme and Altman Solan as our partners.

#### **CUSTOMER SOLUTIONS ADVISOR**

BANK OF NEW ZEALAND | APRIL 2019-FEB 2021

- Worked alongside bankers and various banking teams to give clients the best customer service whilst solving their banking queries.
- Resolved more than 900 customer queries and recovered \$10k worth of funds for customers lost in scams.
- Utilised banking and enterprise software/systems such as SAP, Salesforce, CRM software, Interact, BIS banking software.

# **EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

#### **CO-MEDIA OFFICER**

#### AUCKLAND UNIVERSITY COMMERECE STUDENTS' ASSOCIATION | 2021

- Responsible for creating and maintaining the organisation's digital face through interactive posts on various social media platforms.
- Effective marketing of the association resulted in more than 160 students signing up despite University being online. It also resulted in companies such as MYOB, CAANZ and CPA sponsoring us in 2021.

## **SAVY CHARITABLE TRUST**

FACILLITATOR | 2020 & 2021

- Conducting financial workshops at various High Schools in Auckland
- Educating the youth on financial literacy, budgeting, credit cards and StudyLink

#### **TV HOST**

## APNA TELEVISION | OCT 2019

- Hosted a special segment for the Auckland Board Elections in 2019
- Prepared questions to interviewed candidates from various parties and boards to understand their vision and what they can bring to the community

#### **MEMBER OF UNIVERSITY CLUBS**

- Marketing & Design Club, Women in Business, AUCSA, Auckland University Strength Society, Social Innovation
- Performer and Choreographer for Auckland University Bhangra, and representing the university at cultural events like Auckland Diwali

# **AWARDS & ACHIEVEMENTS**

- B1 Zumba Instructor Certification
- Excellence in Consumer Behaviour (Top percentile in Marketing303)

